RG 062:004, Town of Avon
Connecticut State Library
Town of Avon records
1830-1880
Connecticut State Library
Avon (Conn.)
3.5 cubic feet
Tax, election, school, financial, military, and vital records for the town of Avon.
RG062_004
T000586
Historical Note
The town of Avon was incorporated in May 1830 and was taken from Farmington.
Scope and Content
Tax, election, school, financial, military, and vital records for the town of Avon.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Avon -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Avon -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Avon -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Avon -- Registers; Voting -- Statistics --Connecticut -- Avon; Elections -- Statistics --Connecticut -- Avon; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Avon; School enrollment --Connecticut -- Avon -- Statistics
Places:
Avon (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Avon (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1830-1880
  - Grand lists, 1871-1877, 1880 (Box Box 1)
  - Individual tax lists, 1869, 1879 (Box Box 1)
  - Election returns, 1870-1880 (Box Box 1)
  - Abstracts of births, marriages and deaths, 1852-1880 (Box Box 1)
  - Reports of town officials, 1843-1873 (Box Box 1)
  - Notices of stock holdings and other financial records, including writs of attachment, 1848-1874 (Box Box 1)
  - School registers, 1879-1880 (Box Box 1)
  - Vital records (copy), 1852-1868 (Box Box 1)
  - Complaints, notices, military enrollments and other assorted records, 1879-1907 (Box Box 1)
  - Tax abstracts
    - 1830-1832, 1850, 1851, 1852, 1853-1854, 1855, 1856-1857, 1858-1859, 1860, 1861 (Box Box 2)
    - 1862, 1863, 1864-1865, 1866-1867, 1868, 1869, 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873 (Box Box 3)
    - 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1880 (Box Box 4)
  - List of Electors, 1868